<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
               <preferences version="10.0">
               
  <category name="Active Workspace Viewer">
    <category_description>Active Workspace Viewer-specific preferences.</category_description>
    
               <preference name="AWC_visMaterial" type="Integer" array="false" disabled="false" protectionScope="User" envEnabled="false">
      <preference_description>Specifies the default object material for the Viewer in the Active Workspace client.
Valid values are integers from 0 to 29.
* 0 : SHINY METAL : Sets the object material to SHINY METAL
* 1 : BRUSHED METAL : Sets the object material to BRUSHED METAL
* 2 : SHINY PLASTIC : Sets the object material to SHINY PLASTIC
* 3 : ANALYSIS : Sets the object material to ANALYSIS
* 4 : FLAT : Sets the object material to FLAT. This is the default value.
* 5 : RED GLOSSY PLASTIC : Sets the object material to RED GLOSSY PLASTIC
* 6 : BLUE GLOSSY PLASTIC : Sets the object material to BLUE GLOSSY PLASTIC
* 7 : GREEN GLOSSY PLASTIC : Sets the object material to GREEN GLOSSY PLASTIC
* 8 : GRAY GLOSSY PLASTIC : Sets the object material to GRAY GLOSSY PLASTIC
* 9 : BLACK GLOSSY PLASTIC : Sets the object material to BLACK GLOSSY PLASTIC
* 10 : BROWN GLOSSY PLASTIC : Sets the object material to BROWN GLOSSY PLASTIC
* 11 : YELLOW GLOSSY PLASTIC : Sets the object material to YELLOW GLOSSY PLASTIC
* 12 : TEAL GLOSSY PLASTIC : Sets the object material to TEAL GLOSSY PLASTIC
* 13 : WHITE GLOSSY PLASTIC : Sets the object material to WHITE GLOSSY PLASTIC
* 14 : CLEAR PLASTIC : Sets the object material to CLEAR PLASTIC
* 15 : CHROME : Sets the object material to CHROME
* 16 : COPPER : Sets the object material to COPPER
* 17 : GOLD : Sets the object material to GOLD
* 18 : BRASS : Sets the object material to BRASS
* 19 : STEEL : Sets the object material to STEEL
* 20 : BRUSHED CHROME : Sets the object material to BRUSHED CHROME
* 21 : BRUSHED ALUMINUM : Sets the object material to BRUSHED ALUMINUM
* 22 : BRUSHED TITANIUM : Sets the object material to BRUSHED TITANIUM
* 23 : GLASS : Sets the object material to GLASS
* 24 : SMOKEY GLASS : Sets the object material to SMOKEY GLASS
* 25 : RED PAINT : Sets the object material to RED PAINT
* 26 : GRAY PAINT : Sets the object material to GRAY PAINT
* 27 : BLACK PAINT : Sets the object material to BLACK PAINT
* 28 : BLUE PAINT : Sets the object material to BLUE PAINT
* 29 : RUBBER   : Sets the object material to RUBBER</preference_description>
      <context name="Teamcenter">
        <value>4</value>
      </context>
    </preference>
    
               </category>
               </preferences>
               