<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
               <preferences version="10.0">
               
  <category name="NX">
    <category_description>No description available for this category.</category_description>
    
               <preference name="DATASET_saveas_pattern" type="String" array="false" disabled="false" protectionScope="Site" envEnabled="false">
      <preference_description>Affects the behavior of the Teamcenter SaveAs dialog box as determined by the implementation of the USER_copied_datasets_details and USER_copied_dataset_name user exits.Also affects the behavior of the Teamcenter Integration for NX SaveAs Non-Master Part File 
dialog box in the same manner.This preference is only read by these two user exits.To access the Integration Toolkit Function Reference, install the Teamcenter developer references when you install Teamcenter online help, or go to the Global Technical Access Center (GTAC):
https://support.industrysoftware.automation.siemens.com/docs/teamcenter/
Specifies a pattern used to generate and return the output name of nonmaster items during SaveAs of their master item. The pattern consists of literal text and the following tokens: ${UserText}, ${ItemID} and ${RevisionID}. Existing dataset names are expected to match this pattern, 
where ${ItemID} and ${RevisionID} match the item ID and revision ID of the owning item revision respectively, and ${UserText} matches any text in the original name. For example, a typical pattern is:
${UserText}-${ItemID}/${RevisionID}
where the site has decided that the ${UserText} at the beginning is intended to be the name of the dataset, for example: drawing, and the minus sign (-) is literal text. If you are saving item revision 001234/B to item revision 002345/A, and the dataset&apos;s existing name is drawing-001234/B 
then the name is said to&apos;match against the pattern. Because the ${UserText} at the start of this pattern matches any string, the dataset name fea-001234/B would also match against the pattern. However, drawing_001234/B would not match the pattern as the minus sign is required, and 
drawing-001235/B would not match since the item ID is incorrect.Once an original dataset name has been matched against the pattern, the new dataset name is generated by replacing the ${ItemID} and ${RevisionID} with the new revision and item ID in the pattern, and all occurrences of 
${UserData} with whatever text they matched against in the original name. This new name can then be used for saving the new dataset. Using the example above, the two datasets are saved as drawing-002345/A and fea-002345/A.You can modify these generated names using the 
DATASET_saveas_allow_name_modification preference. However, if the DATASET_saveas_force_name_validation preferences is set to true, the user-edited name is still required to match the pattern.
Valid Values:
${UserText} - Dataset names are copied forward to the new revision unchanged.</preference_description>
      <context name="Teamcenter">
        <value>${ItemID}/${RevisionID}</value>
      </context>
    </preference>
    
               </category>
               </preferences>
               