<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
               <preferences version="10.0">
               
  <category name="Manufacturing">
    <category_description>No description available for this category.</category_description>
    
               <preference name="MEPerspectiveMode" type="String" array="true" disabled="false" protectionScope="User" envEnabled="false">
      <preference_description>Defines the behavior of how views open in manufacturing perspectives. You can specify a mode for each manufacturing perspective in the user interface using the Window-&gt;Perspective Mode menu command. You can set the default mode for each perspective using this preference.
Valid Values:
Accepts a list of strings separated by a colon as follows:
perspective-id:mode

perspective-id:
Specifies the unique name of the manufacturing perspective. The following default perspectives are available by default:
The Manufacturing Process Planner default perspective: com.teamcenter.rac.cme.mpp.MSEPerspectiveThe Manufacturing - Process Sequencing perspective: com.teamcenter.rac.cme.mpp.ProcessSequencing
The Manufacturing - BOM Reconciliation perspective: com.teamcenter.rac.cme.mpp.BOMReconciliation
If you create a new perspective by using the Save Perspective As menu command, you must select the mode using the Window-&gt;Perspective Mode menu command.

mode:
Specifies how the views open in the perspective. There are two options:

OpenExplicitOnly :  Opens structures in existing views where available. Any other open but not yet loaded structures are only opened in a view when explicitly opened (for example,
by right-clicking the structure in the Open Items list and choosing Activate). For example, if you send a product with an associated process and plant to the Manufacturing - Process Sequencing
perspective, the following occurs:
The process view is filled because the Manufacturing - Process Sequencing perspective contains an empty process view.
The product opens in a new view because you opened it explicitly (sent the product to the perspective).
The plant is loaded, but no view opens for it because it was implicitly opened and there was no empty plant view available for it in the perspective.
Prior to Teamcenter 10.0, manufacturing perspectives open structures using the OpenExplicitOnly mode.

OpenAllStrategy : Teamcenter opens a new view for each structure being opened. When objects are opened in another perspective,Teamcenter opens a new view for 
them in this perspective as well.</preference_description>
      <context name="Teamcenter">
        <value>com.teamcenter.rac.cme.mpp.MSEPerspective:OpenAllStrategy</value>
        <value>com.teamcenter.rac.se.ui.SystemsEngineeringPerspective:OpenAllStrategy</value>
        <value>com.teamcenter.rac.cme.mbm.mbmPerspective:OpenAllStrategy</value>
      </context>
    </preference>
    
               </category>
               </preferences>
               