<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
               <preferences version="10.0">
               
  <category name="Manufacturing">
    <category_description>No description available for this category.</category_description>
    
               <preference name="MERuleForBriefcaseExport" type="String" array="true" disabled="false" protectionScope="User" envEnabled="false">
      <preference_description>Defines the rule to govern creation of Appearence Path Node (APN) for the lines during briefcase export of  Collaboration Context.
This will help the recepient of exported data to perform certain operations such as consumption of product to Bill of Processes (BOP).

Valid values are in the format &quot;Type:StructureType; ClosureRule:ClosureRuleName; Lines:LinesValue;&quot;, where
- StructureType: Specifies the type of structure from which BOMLines are identified. Valid Values:
* Item : Product structure.
* MEWorkarea : Workarea structure.
* Mfg0MEPlantBOP: Plant Bill of Processes (BOP).
* MEProcess: BOP.
* Mfg0MEStudy: Study Structure.

- ClosureRuleName: Specifies the name of closure rule to be run on structure defined in Type. The closure rule can be blank. User defined closure rule is also accepted.

- LinesValue: Specifies the candidate lines for which APN is to be created. This option is ignored if valid closure rule is provided. This can be blank. Valid Values:
* For &quot;Item&quot; and &quot;MEWorkarea&quot; Type :
+ AllLines : All lines in structures.
+ HierarchyOfConsumedLinesOnly : All lines in the hierarachy of Product/Plant lines consumed in a Process/Plant BOP structure.
+ HierarchyOfConsumedLinesAndSiblingsOnly : All lines which are in the hierarachy and are the siblings of Product/Plant lines consumed in a Process/Plant BOP structure.
+ HierarchyOfConsumedLinesAndHierarchyOfSiblings : All lines which are in the hierarachy and are the siblings and are in the hierarachy of siblings of Product/Plant lines consumed in a Process/Plant BOP structure.
* For &quot;BOP&quot; and &quot;Study&quot; Type:
+ AllLines : For all lines in the BOP and Study structures.
+ Process : For all processes.
+ Operation : For all operations.

Some examples of the usage of this preference are:
-&quot;Type:Item; Lines:HierarchyOfConsumedLinesOnly;&quot;
Appearence Path Node (APN) will be created for all the lines in the hierarchy of product lines consumed in BOP or Study structure.

- &quot;Type:MEWorkarea; Lines:HierarchyOfConsumedLinesAndSiblingsOnly;&quot;
Appearence Path Node (APN) will be created for all the lines which are in the hierarchy and which are the siblings of plant lines consumed in BOP or Study structure.

- &quot;Type:Mfg0MEStudy; ClosureRule:MFGEBOPExportDefault; Lines:Process;&quot;
The value provided in the Lines option will be ignored and closure rule will be used.

- &quot;Type:Mfg0MEPlantBOP; ClosureRule:; Lines:HierarchyOfConsumedLinesOnly;&quot;
Notice the invalid value for Lines. This will be ignored and Appearence Path Node (APN) will not be created for any line under the Plant BOP structure.

- &quot;Type:MEProcess; ClosureRule:; Lines:;&quot;
Neither Closure Rule nor the Lines option value is specified. Thus, Appearence Path Node (APN) will not be created for any line under the Process structure.

One type can be specified only once in the preference value. If specified multiple times, the first value will be considered and the others will be ignored.
For example, if the values are &quot;Type:Item; ClosureRule:; Lines:HierarchyOfConsumedLinesOnly;&quot; and &quot;Type:Item; ClosureRule:MFGEBOPExportDefault; Lines:;&quot;, the first value will be considered and the second one will be ignored.

The default values for the preference is &quot;Type:Item; ClosureRule:; Lines:AllLines;&quot;
&quot;Type:MEWorkarea; ClosureRule:; Lines:AllLines;&quot;
Type:Mfg0MEPlantBOP; ClosureRule:; Lines:AllLines;.</preference_description>
      <context name="Teamcenter">
        <value>Type:Item; ClosureRule:; Lines:AllLines;</value>
        <value>Type:MEWorkarea; ClosureRule:; Lines:AllLines;</value>
        <value>Type:Mfg0MEPlantBOP; ClosureRule:; Lines:AllLines;</value>
      </context>
    </preference>
    
               </category>
               </preferences>
               