<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
               <preferences version="10.0">
               
  <category name="Schedule Manager">
    <category_description>Allows configuring of Schedule Manager functionality.</category_description>
    
               <preference name="ProgramViewFilterProperties" type="String" array="true" disabled="false" protectionScope="Site" envEnabled="false">
      <preference_description>Specifies the list of attributes for schedule and schedule task objects displayed in the Filter dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
Valid Values:
Schedule Task.complete_percent - Displays complete percent in the Filter dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
Schedule Task.actual_start_date - Displays actual start date in the Filter dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
Schedule Task.actual_finish_date - Displays actual finish date in the Filter dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
Schedule Task.work_complete - Displays work complete in the Filter dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
Schedule Task.ResourceAssignment - Displays resource assignment in the Filter dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
Schedule Task.object_desc - Displays object description in the Filter dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
Schedule Task.duration - Displays duration in the Filter dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
Schedule Task.object_name - Displays object name in the Filter dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
Schedule Task.priority - Displays priority in the Filter dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
Schedule Task.start_date - Displays start date in the Filter dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
Schedule Task.finish_date - Displays finish date in the Filter dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
Schedule Task.work_estimate - Displays work estimate in the Filter dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
Schedule Task.fnd0state - Displays state in the Filter dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
Schedule Task.fnd0status - Displays status in the Filter dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
Schedule.object_name - Displays object name in the Filter dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.</preference_description>
      <context name="Teamcenter">
        <value>ScheduleTask.complete_percent</value>
        <value>ScheduleTask.actual_start_date</value>
        <value>ScheduleTask.actual_finish_date</value>
        <value>ScheduleTask.work_complete</value>
        <value>ScheduleTask.ResourceAssignment</value>
        <value>ScheduleTask.object_desc</value>
        <value>ScheduleTask.duration</value>
        <value>ScheduleTask.object_name</value>
        <value>ScheduleTask.priority</value>
        <value>ScheduleTask.start_date</value>
        <value>ScheduleTask.finish_date</value>
        <value>ScheduleTask.work_estimate</value>
        <value>ScheduleTask.fnd0state</value>
        <value>ScheduleTask.fnd0status</value>
        <value>Schedule.object_name</value>
      </context>
    </preference>
    
               </category>
               </preferences>
               