<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
               <preferences version="10.0">
               
  <category name="Column Preferences">
    <category_description>No description available for this category.</category_description>
    
               <preference name="ScheduleColumnsShownPref" type="String" array="true" disabled="false" protectionScope="User" envEnabled="false">
      <preference_description>Specifies the Schedule Task object attributes displayed in the Column Chooser dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a Program View is opened.
Valid Values:
ScheduleTask.start_date - Displays start date in the Column Chooser dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
ScheduleTask.finish_date - Displays finish date in the Column Chooser dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
ScheduleTask.duration - Displays duration in the Column Chooser dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
ScheduleTask.work_estimate - Displays work estimate in the Column Chooser dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
ScheduleTask.task_type - Displays task type in the Column Chooser dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
ScheduleTask.constraint - Displays constraint in the Column Chooser dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
ScheduleTask.actual_start_date - Displays actual start date in the Column Chooser dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
ScheduleTask.actual_finish_date - Displays actual finish date in the Column Chooser dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
ScheduleTask.work_complete - Displays work complete in the Column Chooser dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
ScheduleTask.complete_percent - Displays complete percent in the Column Chooser dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
ScheduleTask.fnd0state - Displays find state in the Column Chooser dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
ScheduleTask.fnd0status - Displays find status in the Column Chooser dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
ScheduleTask.SI - Displays SI in the Column Chooser dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
ScheduleTask.object_name - Displays object name in the Column Chooser dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
ScheduleTask.ResourceAssignment - Displays resource assignment in the Column Chooser dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
predecessors - Displays predecessors in the Column Chooser dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.
successors - Displays successors in the Column Chooser dialog box of the Schedule Manager application when a program view is opened.</preference_description>
      <context name="Teamcenter">
        <value>ScheduleTask.start_date</value>
        <value>ScheduleTask.finish_date</value>
        <value>ScheduleTask.duration</value>
        <value>ScheduleTask.work_estimate</value>
        <value>ScheduleTask.task_type</value>
        <value>ScheduleTask.constraint</value>
        <value>ScheduleTask.actual_start_date</value>
        <value>ScheduleTask.actual_finish_date</value>
        <value>ScheduleTask.work_complete</value>
        <value>ScheduleTask.complete_percent</value>
        <value>ScheduleTask.fnd0state</value>
        <value>ScheduleTask.fnd0status</value>
        <value>ScheduleTask.SI</value>
        <value>ScheduleTask.object_name</value>
        <value>ScheduleTask.ResourceAssignment</value>
        <value>predecessors</value>
        <value>successors</value>
      </context>
    </preference>
    
               </category>
               </preferences>
               