<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
               <preferences version="10.0">
               
  <category name="General">
    <category_description>No description available for this category.</category_description>
    
               <preference name="TC_config_condition_max_normalization_effort" type="Integer" array="false" disabled="false" protectionScope="Site" envEnabled="false">
      <preference_description>Selects the strategy for normalizing configuration expressions such as variant conditions.
This nornalization process is executed as part of saving the expression and automatically transforms the configuration expression into one or more Normal Forms (Conjunctive Normal Form - CNF or Disjunctive Normal Form - DNF). A CNF based normalization strategy is used if the estimated number of DNF terms (without removing redundancy) is less than the value defined by this preference.
If the estimated number of DNF terms exceeds the preference value a DNF based strategy is selected, which is expected to result in a (usually significantly) smaller normalization result, but which is less optimal when evaluating configuration criteria.
Since the estimate cannot take the effect of redundancy removal into account (a welcome by-product of the normalization process), the preference value significally overshoots the actual result.
However, how much overshoot is acceptable depends on the nature and complexity of the configuration expression.
Empirical analysis suggests that a good value is 30000 to reach a reasonable balance between save performance and configuration criteria evaluation performance.
Valid values are all positive integer numbers greater or equal to 2. However, values less than the value for the preference &quot;TC_max_cnf_count_for_condition_normalization&quot; are not practical.</preference_description>
      <context name="Teamcenter">
        <value>30000</value>
      </context>
    </preference>
    
               </category>
               </preferences>
               