<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
               <preferences version="10.0">
               
  <category name="General">
    <category_description>No description available for this category.</category_description>
    
               <preference name="TC_remote_checkin_assy_option" type="Integer" array="false" disabled="false" protectionScope="User" envEnabled="false">
      <preference_description>Determines how the system manages newly added components when a remotely checked out BOM view revision (BVR) or item revision is remotely checked in. The typical use case is for a remote user to remotely check out a BVR to add new components owned by the local site (the site adding the component). 
When the BVR is remotely checked in, this preference determines how these locally owned components are handled.This preference is deprecated as of Teamcenter 10.1.1; it will be removed in a future release, and should not be used. This functionality has been replaced by options in the standard Teamcenter import and 
export options dialog boxes. Teamcenter ignores the preference setting when any import or export option is selected in the dialog box.
Valid Values:
0 - The components are stubbed upon remote check in. A copy is not sent to the site that owns the BVR. Instead, at the owning site, the component is replaced by a POM stub. When the assembly containing the BVR is opened at the owning site via Structure Manager, the application prompts the user to remotely import the component.
1 - The components are sent to the owning site as replicas. Site ownership of the components remains with the site performing the remote checkin.
2 - Site ownership of the components is transferred to the site that owns the BVR. The components at the site performing the remote check in become replicas.</preference_description>
      <context name="Teamcenter">
        <value>1</value>
      </context>
    </preference>
    
               </category>
               </preferences>
               