<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
               <preferences version="10.0">
               
  <category name="General">
    <category_description>No description available for this category.</category_description>
    
               <preference name="UGMASTER_saveas_pattern" type="String" array="false" disabled="false" protectionScope="Site" envEnabled="false">
      <preference_description>Defines the pattern string of the name of new UGMASTER dataset object during a &quot;Save As&quot; operation. Value may contain text and also refer to the content of some of the object&apos;s properties using the ${PropertyName} format, with PropertyName being ItemID, RevisionID or UserText. Existing dataset name is expected to match this pattern. If the existing dataset name does not match the pattern, then the new dataset name will not follow this pattern.
Example: ${UserText}-${ItemID}/${RevisionID} where the site has decided that the ${UserText} at the beginning is intended to be the name of the dataset, and the minus sign is literal text. Suppose a user is saving item revision 001234/B to item revision 002345/A. If a dataset&apos;s existing name is &quot;master-001234/B&quot; then the name is said to &apos;match&apos; against the pattern. Since the ${UserText} at the start of this pattern matches any string, dataset name &quot;fea-001234/B&quot; would also match against the pattern. However, &quot;master_001234/B&quot; would not match the pattern as the minus sign is required, and &quot;master-001235/B&quot; would not match since the ItemID is incorrect. Once an original dataset name has been matched against the pattern, the new dataset name is generated by replacing the ${ItemID} and ${RevisionID} with the new revision and ItemID in the pattern, and all occurrences of ${UserData} with whatever text they matched against in the original name. This new name can then be used for saving the new dataset. Using the example above, the dataset would be saved as &quot;master-002345/A&quot;.
This is a site preference.</preference_description>
      <context name="Teamcenter">
        <value>${ItemID}-${RevisionID}</value>
      </context>
    </preference>
    
               </category>
               </preferences>
               